Exercise 1-51 Description and Set Phrase Test Let's check and see if the concepts
are clear. Underline or highlight the stressed word. Repeat after me. 1. He's a
nice guy. 2. He's an American guy from San Francisco. 3. The cheerleader needs a
rubber band to hold her ponytail. 4. The executive assistant needs a paper clip for
the final report.
5. The law student took an English test in a foreign country.
6. The policeman saw a red car on the freeway in Los Angeles.
7. My old dog has long ears and a flea problem.
8. The new teacher broke his coffee cup on the first day.
9. His best friend has a broken cup in his other office.
10. Let's play football on the weekend in New York.
11. Jingle bells is a nice song. 12. Where are my new shoes? 13. Where are my tennis
shoes? 14. I have a headache from the heat wave in South Carolina. 15. The newlyweds
took a long walk in Long Beach. 16. The little dog was sitting on the sidewalk.
17. The famous athlete changed clothes in the locker room. 18. The art exhibit was
held in an empty room. 19. There was a class reunion at the high school. 20. The
headlines indicated a new policy. 21. We got online and went to AmericanAccent
.com 22. The stock options were listed in the company directory. 23. All the second
graders were out on the playground.